https://entkent.com/legal-notices/

HomeMedical InformationEar ConditionsMicrosuction of EarBAHA Auditory ImplantCholesteatoma and Mastoid SurgeryDizziness and VertigoGlue Ear, Grommets and AdenoidsOtitis ExternaHow to use ear dropsTinnitusNose ConditionsRhino SinusitisFESS Sinus SurgeryNosebleedsRigid Nasal Sinus EndoscopyFlexible Fibreoptic Naso – LaryngoscopyThroat ConditionsTonsils and AdenoidsFlexible Fibreoptic Naso – LaryngoscopyMedical InformationBiofilms and InfectionWhat to do in an EmergencyServices and FeesServicesWhat We DoConsultationsOut Patient ProceduresOperationsBAHA Auditory ImplantExpert WitnessENT ProceduresMicrosuction of EarRigid Nasal Sinus EndoscopyFlexible Fibreoptic Naso – LaryngoscopyOur FeesENT Specialist Fees Consultations Out Patient ProceduresExpert Witness feesPrivate Patient feesAbout UsAbout UsOur Admin TeamTestimonialsRatings & Reviews on iWantGreatCareCredentialsView DiplomasCurriculum vitae James W Fairley Consultant Otorhinolaryngologist – ENT Specialist Physician and SurgeonMedicolegal CVPublicationsEvidence Based MedicineMasters ThesisAppointmentsContactContact usInformation for Medical SecretariesInformation for Legal Secretaries and Medical Report AgenciesWhat to do in an EmergencyLegal notices: Terms of UseThis page last updated 19 June 2020Access to the public area of this website entkent.com is provided to you free of charge and without any requirement to register your personal details with us. By using this website you signify agreement to the terms of use as contained in the following disclaimer, limitation of liablity, links, jurisdiction, copyright and personal privacy notices.DisclaimerAll information and advice on this website is of a general nature and may not apply to you. Although we take care to update our pages regularly, medical knowledge is constantly advancing, and we cannot promise that all the information will always be up to date and accurate. Medical information on this site is provided to enhance and complement, not replace, advice from a qualified medical practitioner. There is no substitute for an individual consultation. We recommend that you see your General Practitioner if you would like to be referred.Limitation of liablityNeither Mr James W. Fairley nor Mrs Sylvia A. Fairley will accept liability for any loss or damages arising from your use of information contained within or accessed via the entkent.com website. We cannot guarantee uninterrupted access to the website and you should not rely on it being permanently available online. This does not affect your statutory rights and we do not seek to exclude or limit our liablity for death or personal injury caused by our negligence, fraudulent misrepresentation, or any other act not capable of being excluded under English Law.LinksLinks to third party websites are provided for your convenience and ease of use. We do not have any control over the continued availablity, quality or relevance of the content of third party websites. The presence of a link from this website does not necessarily imply our endorsement or recommendation of the owners, operators, products, services or content of the linked website.JurisdictionThis website is based in England. By using this website you agree that such use is subject to English Law. Any dispute arising from your use of this site will be determined exclusively in the English Courts.Copyright / intellectual propertyExcept where otherwise identified, the original images and written material on this site are the intellectual property and / or copyright of Mr James W. Fairley who asserts all his moral rights as the author of the work. The information may be freely reproduced in its entirety by photocopying, print, electronic publishing or any other means on condition that no additions, deletions or any other alterations are made to the text, that the authorship is acknowledged, and that the information is circulated for the benefit of patients. Extracts may be made for personal use or study but commercial use is prohibited without express prior permission. If any of the material presented on this site is subject to additional restrictions then you must abide by those restrictions.Personal privacyWe do not collect personal data about you when you visit this the public areas of this website. If you leave contact details on our feedback form, we will not share those details with any third party. Our website hosting service automatically collects information on the IP address (a code that identifes your computer’s link to the internet), pages visited, times of day, and types of browser used by visitors to the site. This information is used in aggregate form only. There is no intention to obtain or use personal data by this means. Any data thus collected which could identify an individual will be handled by us in compliance with the terms of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) as it applies in the UK under the Data Protection Act 2018, and in accordance with the terms of our registration with the UK
Information Commissioner’s Office. We use Google Analytics to analyze the audience of the website and improve our content. No personal information is collected from Google Analytics. For further information on the privacy policy concerning Google Analytics, please visit https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=enWhat are cookies?Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or device when you visit a website. They are widely used in order to make websites work more efficiently and provide basic functionality such as remembering preferences or filling out forms. They are also used to provide information and insights to the owners of the site that help to improve performance and offer a better user experience.Cookies on entkent.comThis site uses cookies. The table below explains the cookies we use and why. We will not use any of this data to personally identify you.CookieNamePurposeGoogle Analytics_ga_gat_gidThese cookies are used to collect information about how you use our website. The information collected includes number of visitors, pages visited and time spent on the website. The information is collected by Google Analytics in aggregated and anonymous form, and we use the data to help us make improvements to the website. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.Click here for more information about Google Analytics and your privacy.Session cookiesDYNSRVThese cookies are used for the website to function and to improve the performance of the website. Disabling cookiesYou can prevent the use of cookies by adjusting the cookie settings by clicking the tab in the bottom right hand corner of the screen on this page or by adjusting your browser settings.Please be aware that some cookies are necessary for the website to function. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of this site and many other sites you visit will then not then work properly as certain functionality and features will have been disabled.For more information about cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ Compliance with UK standardsThis website has been written to comply with current UK standards regarding the publishing of medical service information and conform with guidelines published by the General Medical Council in “Good Medical Practice” 2013.Comments and complaintsIf you have a comment or complaint about the content of this site please contact us in writing at 71 Mill Court, Ashford, Kent TN24 8DN, by telephone 01233 642244, or by email admin@entkent.com
We comply with the HONcode standard for trustworthy health information:verify here.DisclaimerAll information and advice on this website is of a general nature and may not apply to you. This medical information is provided to enhance and support, not replace, individual advice from a qualified medical practitioner. Please see our Terms of Use.
